shoplet.com 2016-06-08

# Privacy Statement

Shoplet.com operates one of the world's largest Internet superstores in terms of office, computer hardware, software, tools & hardware, networking, furniture, supplies and cleaning & maintenance. It is our goal to offer competitive pricing, innovative use of technology, unparalleled product selection, value-added content and a high level of personalized service.

We use your e-mail address to send verification of your purchase or to notify you if a product is on back order. Your telephone number is used only if we have a question about your order and need to reach you quickly about your order.

Several sections of our site offer links to other sites. Although we make every effort to select sites that we feel are of interest to our customers, we cannot guarantee your privacy when linking to one of these sites.

**Information Collection and Use**

Shoplet.com will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Shoplet.com collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

**Order**

We request information from the user on our order form. Here, a user must provide contact information like name and shipping address, and financial information like credit card number and expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill a customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.

**Price Alert**

To better service our customers, we offer an email notification system whereby customers provide us with their email, name and a target price for an item which we will use to notify them by email when the item hits the target price.

**Affiliate Program**

For those wishing to become an affiliate, we request the name, company, address, and contact information. In addition, we request the website that we will be affiliated with as well as information about the website and company structure for billing purposes. An email notification will be sent once the affiliate's application has been reviewed along with instructions for how to tag and become a Shoplet.com affiliate.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. We use cookies to track your stay at our store. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. For instance, allowing us to set a cookie will track the products you put in your shopping cart. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our personalization and customization features. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

**Log Files**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Sharing**

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

We partner with certain third parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

Shoplet may disclose personal information as reasonably necessary to: (a) satisfy applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce any and all applicable terms of service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Shoplet, its customers or the public as required or permitted by law.

**Links**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Shoplet.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Shoplet.com.

**Newsletter**

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. The user can unsubscribe at any given time after subscribing to the newsletter.

**E-mail this page**

If a user elects to use our referral service to inform a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. Shoplet.com will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Shoplet.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact us to request the removal of this information from our database. 

**Security**

Shoplet.com takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When the user submits sensitive information via the website, their information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of web browsers, such as Microsoft Internet Explorer, becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just "surfing."

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to regain access to private user information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up to date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment, in a locked room.

If you have any questions about our website's security, please contact us.

**Supplementation of Information**

In order for Shoplet.com to tailor the user experience to an individual's preferences, we combine information about user purchasing habits with similar information from our partners to create a personalized user profile. When a user makes a purchase from either of these two companies, the companies collect and share that purchase information with us so we can tailor the site to our users' preferences.

**Special Offers**

We send all new members a welcome email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information about products, services, special deals, as well as a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to opt out of these types of communications. 

**Site and Service Updates**

We also send site and service announcement updates to our users. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements because they contain important information about our service. We communicate with users via email or phone when there are issues relating to their account.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**

At any time and as often as necessary, Shoplet.com offers users the ability to correct or change the information submitted during registration. You can access and change this information after signing into your account and going to your account settings. Users who are experiencing problems, or who have any questions about how our services work, can contact us.

**Choice/Opt-out**

Our users are given the opportunity to opt-out of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site and/or to the third party service(s) the user requested at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an opt-out mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the top of any Shoplet newsletter.

**California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to: 

Leslie Scharf   
SVP and General Counsel   
Ellison Systems, Inc. d/b/a Shoplet.com  
39 Broadway, Suite 2030   
New York, New York 10006

**US-EU Safe Harbor Framework Compliance**

Shoplet.com complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Shoplet.com has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Shoplet.com's certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

**US-EU Safe Harbor Framework - Dispute Resolution**

In the event that a dispute arises relating to Shoplet.com's compliance with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework, Shoplet.com has selected as an independent resource mechanism and agrees to utilize the services and procedures provided by the American Arbitration Association, to preside over and hear any and all complaints with respect to compliance with the Framework(s). Additionally, Shoplet.com hereby agrees to comply with the EU Data Protection Authorities (DPAs) to investigate any and all unresolved complaints.

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

**Contact Info**

Email Us   
1.800.757.3015 (9am to 6pm EST Monday through Friday)   
39 Broadway, Suite 2030 | New York, NY 10006
